Talha Khan

Social Media Executive

Lahore 54000

talhakhank91xnc3c_gik@indeedemail.com

+920303 0650735

I'm passionate, high lots of adroit skills which help in growing my sentiments in Social Media Marketing. I can raise website traffic, brand awareness by driving effective campaigns. My additional expertise in social media post designing & social media optimization is valuable.

Work Experience

Social Media marketing manager

Kamboh softec-Lahore August 2023 to July 2024

In this Company, my role is high lots of adroit skills which help in growing my sentiments in Social Media Marketing. I can raise website traffic, brand awareness by driving effective campaigns. My additional expertise in social media post designing, customer support, & social media optimization is valuable.

Social Media Executive

Muhammadi estate-Lahore October 2022 to March 2023

In this Company, my role is high lots of adroit skills which help in growing my sentiments in Social Media Marketing. I can raise website traffic, brand awareness by driving effective campaigns. My additional expertise in social media post designing, customer support, & social media optimization is valuable.

Social Media Executive

Dexpel-Lahore

May 2022 to September 2022

In this Company, my role is high lots of adroit skills which help in growing my sentiments in Social Media Marketing. I can raise website traffic, brand awareness by driving effective campaigns. My additional expertise in social media post designing, Shopify handling, customer support & social media optimization is valuable.

Social Media Executive

Dots in Blue-Lahore

December 2020 to May 2022

In this Company, my role is high lots of adroit skills which help in growing my sentiments in Social Media Marketing. I can raise website traffic, brand awareness by driving effective campaigns. My additional expertise in social media post designing, WordPress & social media optimization is valuable.

Business Development Team Intern

House of Solution-Lahore July 2020 to November 2020

In this Company, my role is high lots of adroit skills which help in growing my sentiments in Business development.

Education

Bachelor's in Computer Science

University of South Asia - Lahore February 2016 to December 2020

Skills

- Digital Marketing (2 years)
- Social Media Management (4 years)
- WordPress (1 year)
- Graphic Design (2 years)
- Content Creation (1 year)
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO) (Less than 1 year)
- Video Editing (1 year)
- Email Marketing (Less than 1 year)

Languages

- Chinese Beginner
- English Intermediate
- Urdu Fluent
- Punjabi Fluent

Certifications and Licenses

Digital Marketing

November 2020 to March 2021